What's the matter?
You can't stand?
Charanko, what have you been
doing here the last six months?
Didn't I tell you that if you were
going to become my student,
you needed to train like
your life depended on it?
You won't be able to learn any techniques.
You're not fit to be a martial artist.
I am expelling you from
this dojo as of today.
Don't ever come back again.
Bang is acting strange?
He suddenly said we were going to do a
lesson, then beat the crap out of me.
I can't believe someone as kind
as Master Bang would do this.
There has to be a reason.
I came here because I thought
you guys might know something.
I have no idea.
Bang? You mean the Class S Silverfang?
Once you're done talking,
let's continue our game.
There seem to be more of you here now...
I can at least guess what's going on.
I'm assuming that Garo is somehow involved.
Garo?!
You mean the guy who was expelled
from our dojo? Why him?
What? You haven't heard?
Bang's former disciple, Garo,
has been classified as an evil monster
and is wanted by the Hero Association.
Bang said he'd bring him down himself.
Monster? Garo?
Apparently, there was an incident
at the Hero Association HQ.
The Association's trying to hide it,
but if there's an intense battle,
bystanders are sure to get hurt.
That's probably why Bang wanted
to distance you from it all.
I see...
Master Bang, am I just holding you back?
What do you think about Bang's
actions, Master Saitama?
It's not like I'm that
close with that old man.
Silverfang, huh?
That's such a good hero name.
What the hell is "Bald Cape"
even supposed to mean?
There's one thing that's bothering me.
Who are you?
Master, he's some small fry named Charanko.
He's Bang's current number one student.
We've met him before.
Huh? Have we?
I can't keep holding him back forever.
I need to take care of Garo for Master Bang.
But I guess there's no way
I'll find him that easily.
Even if I happen to find Garo, I—
Hey, you.
You're a hero, aren't you?
I am indeed. My name is Mumen Rider.
I'm going to hunt you.
What do you mean by "hunt"?
You don't seem like a fan of mine.
Help me become a true monster.
Found you!
You sure that's him?
It sure is.
Hey! I came to repay you for the other da—
You came to get revenge,
Tank-Top Vegetarian?
Well, aren't you an adorable fool,
coming here to throw away the life you
were given a second chance at?
I'll kill the rest of your
musclehead buddies, too.
Die!
What?
I heard you gave my bro a hard time.
A Class S?!
I've caught a big one!
This is great! I'm getting all fired up!
Tank-Top Tackle!
There it is! Master's Tank-Top Tackle!
He's taken down countless
monsters with that move!
Way to go, Master! Now that bastard—
Bro, he didn't go down!
All right, Little Bro. Prepare to run!
Is he really...
human?
Is everything ready?
I'm an old man with no family.
Just like you.
You can't be serious.
I've said goodbye to several hundred pupils.
You dropped everything to help out
your precious little brother.
You're so cool, Big Brother.
If we left Garo alone, he'd eventually
come for my dojo, as well.
All right, let's go!
Be careful, Big Brother.
I can't even imagine how powerful he is now,
Considering you took the time to summon me...
There's another one! Tank-Top Punch!
I freaked out for a second when he
stood up after Master's tackle, but...
This will probably be over soon.
He's human. There's no doubt about that.
Still, I wonder why...
I feel like I need to make
him disappear here and now.
Sorry, but this is the end.
Hold it right there!
Mumen Rider!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?!
You're a Class S hero, and you're
trying to finish off a human?!
This fight is over!
It's his fault for picking
a fight with a hero!
Get out of the way!
We're gonna show this guy
how terrifying we are!
All of you, stop.
He's right.
I didn't start wearing a tank-top
just so I could fight with humans.
Hey, you.
If you've learned your lesson, swear that
you'll never hurt anyone ever again.
Fine...
I'm going home. Sorry for losing control.
As if.
I'm still going to murder all of you!
Yeah. I figured as much.
I'll take care of you, here and now.
Whoops. Guess I used it.
I wanted to avoid it since it reminds
me of the old man, but whatever.
He...
He was hiding his true abilities!
Oh, what's this?
A mighty Class S hero is on his knees?
Don't underestimate me. You just
took me by surprise, that's all.
You can just sit there and watch
as the Monster Garo finishes off
every last member of your crew.
Garo?! You're Garo, the human
calling himself a monster?!
W-Wait! Don't touch them!
Justice Crash!
Well? Come at me.
Garo!
I know your fighting style now.
I'm done with you, Tank-Top Master.
Now, then... I guess I'd better
clean up the rest of you.
You bastard! You really think
you can beat our numbers?!
Why, you—
You're finished, Garo!
You've brought shame upon our dojo!
Take this! Fist of Flowing
Water, Crushed Rock!
This is awful.
Looks like we were a little too late.
Bang, can you predict where
he might show up next?
Bang?
Charanko...
I heard that Tank-Top Master got
taken out by the hero hunter.
You can't be serious.
Even a Class S couldn't defeat him?
Apparently, his followers and Mumen Rider,
who were also there, got beat up, too.
So the guy's going after any hero?
It doesn't even matter if they're
Class A or C? Give me a break...
Quit freaking out, guys.
Let's just catch this hero hunter ourselves!
How?
The guy took out a Class S!
You idiots. He's not some scary monster.
He's just a human.
But I heard that he's a former
student of Silverfang's.
I know some martial arts, too.
If a guy punches like this, you do this.
If he punches like this, you go like, "bam!"
And if he goes like this, you do... this!
There he is.
I'm glad you came to visit me, Saitama.
Sure. Can I put the bananas here?
Yeah, thanks.
Of course you're eating them...
It was all over the
Hero Association newspaper.
A single monster took out dozens of heroes.
Glad to see you made it out alive.
Here, have a banana.
He was a human.
Huh?
A human calling himself a monster.
But he's strong.
He's a terrifyingly strong human.
Who was stronger, the fish monster or him?
Hmm... The Deep Sea King was pretty insane,
but there's something different this time.
His techniques.
He's an expert martial artist.
It appears that Silverfang
raised one nasty monster.
This dude just jumped into our conversation.
Do you have any idea who he is?
You know. He's the Class
S hero, Tank-Top Master.
Oh, yeah. You were in the paper, too.
It said you got your ass beat the worst.
Can't you just say I stood my ground the most?!
Damn! To think I'd let such a kid
get the better of me...
Martial arts can be such a pain in the ass.
Martial arts?
Here, have a banana.
Oh... Thanks.
Now, could you tell me more about this guy?
Hey, kid.
Looks like you're reading
something interesting.
This guy's the Class S hero, King.
He's the strongest one of all.
This is the Class A hero, Lightning Genji.
He's always patrolling my neighborhood.
Look! I even got his autograph!
His autograph, eh?
I'd love his autograph, too.
Could you introduce me sometime?
Sure! You must like heroes, too, old dude.
That Hero Guide looks neat.
Say, could I borrow that, just for a week?
What? No way. Get your own.
Jeez, you're so stingy.
Hey, what the heck?
They even have monsters in here!
Isn't that exciting?
What? Why are you excited about the
monster pages? They're super scary.
It's better that they're scary.
Don't you think they're cooler that way?
Really? You have weird taste, old dude.
I'm so envious.
I'd love to be in this book, too.
You want to be a hero?
I do, too... but I have no athletic talent.
Well, good for you.
Your personality sucks, old dude.
Well, then... Time to go patrolling.
I'm heading off.
According to the guide,
this is around the time when the Class A
hero, Golden Ball, visits his favorite bar.
See ya, kid.
Be careful on your patrol, old dude.
Sure. Also, stop calling me "old dude."
Learn how to talk to people.
Huh? What was that, old dude?
Hurry up and go home, kid.
All my attacks were dodged,
parried, and blocked.
He also used throws and counters
against me by reading my moves.
He can deal twice the damage by using
his opponents' strength against them.
The strikes to our joints and
vital points were also brutal.
He also incapacitated physical functions.
Your average monster usually just lets
all its strength loose in a rampage.
But he's different. He has
special techniques to break people.
In other words, he knows
how to take down heroes.
You want to spar with
a strong martial artist?
Yeah.
I'm sorta interested now.
Got any connections,
uh... Champon?
It's Charanko!
Here. I'll even give you a banana.
Don't put that there!
Then just go see Master Bang.
He seems to like you, anyway.
Come on, now.
I can't push around an old guy.
Hey, that's rude!
A normal person can't fight a
martial artist right off the bat, anyway.
First, you have to learn the basic forms...
Actually, before that,
you have to build up stamina.
You can run up and down
hundreds of steps...
Or start by wiping the dojo floors...
Guess I'll leave if you
don't have any connections.
H-Hold on a sec!
There was a mixed martial arts competition
I happened to enter on a whim.
The ticket is... Here you go.
It's all wrinkled.
I registered as a participant,
but I plan to bail.
It still works as an entry ticket, though,
so you can go watch the competition.
You'll be able to see all kinds of styles.
Thanks.
Stare...
So you're going to drop out?
Yeah, I mean, I'm pretty hurt.
Stare...
It says the prize money is three million yen.
Well, it's a huge tournament.
The champion gets three
million in one day's pay.
Stare...
Just so you know, you
can't enter in my place.
Hey. Are you listening to me?
You must be the Class A hero, Golden Ball.
Huh?
Class A Rank 26
Golden Ball
I have some business with you.
Step outside for a bit.
At least let me enjoy a drink first.
Hey, what the hell?! Jeez, what a waste.
Sure, wild guy. There's a parking lot nearby.
Let's go there.
Every once in a while, I get punks
who want to challenge a pro hero.
If you're picking a fight just because
you're drunk, you should reconsider.
This is your chance to bail.
Shut up, you drunk. I'm—
You bastard.
You're way too lax, hero hunter.
Did Tank-Top Master seriously
lose to a punk like you?
Just so you know, I'm pretty
good at hunting, myself.
After I take you down,
I'm gonna go have another drink!
He guessed the bullet's trajectory
by reading my hand movements.
Then how about this?!
A ricochet?
Whoops.
Luckily for you, I missed your vital
points, but what do you think of that?
Aren't heroes amazing?
Luckily? It's because you're
so drunk that your aim is off.
You're going to lose because you couldn't
finish me off with that one shot.
Unfortunately for you,
I've got plenty of ammo left.
Shape-memory Golden Bullets!
Take this!
Killer Move: Golden Breakout!
He's dodging all the bullets
with minimal movement...
This guy's insane!
But... This is my final shot.
I'm going to end this.
How'd you like that?
Aren't monsters amazing?
You're finished.
Die.
You weren't at the bar,
so I thought you had forgotten about our plans.
The Class A hero, Spring Mustachio?
I'm flattered that you've heard of me.
You must be the hero hunter
I keep hearing about.
Ding, ding. For your prize,
I'll crush you now, too.
His right leg's been injured.
That should slow down his footwork.
I see. Thank you for the advice.
Doesn't swinging that thing in a cramped
place like this put you at a disadvantage?
Oh, I'm not so sure about... that!
I have you now!
Tomboy!
I've... got you!
Did you guys know that your trump
cards are listed in the Hero Guide?
Opponents with weapons are easy
once you get used to them.
Hey, don't get ahead of yourself.
You can't keep doing this forever.
I'm going to continue getting stronger.
Just try and take me out if you can!
Until you do, I'll keep doing
whatever the hell I want.
Hey, the Hero Association
makes a lot of money, right?
Don't say things like that.
It costs a lot of money to keep the peace.
It's not like we're loaded.
Then why did you buy this for me?
And why do you always stop by our place?
To keep the peace, of course.
For an official from the Hero Association,
fooling around with you
two is a necessary expense.
As someone who fights evil on the front lines,
I need a way to restore my energy.
Letting loose, eh?
That means you're letting
loose every single day.
Oh, I know. Why don't I introduce
you to Amai Mask next time?
What? Really?
I'm a huge fan of his!
If you give me a kiss on the cheek.
What? I'm not sure about that...
For real? Really?
Let me meet him, too.
I'll gladly kiss you on the cheek.
Letting loose, letting loose.
Life's so peaceful.
I felt great after defeating
those Class A heroes...
Now I feel like I just stepped in shit.
Fighting evil on the front lines?
You make me sick.
Oh, hey. I finally found you.
I've been looking for you.
Reinforcements? Is he a hero, too?
I've never seen him before.
Must be some nameless bottom-ranker.
He's probably trying to catch me
so he can climb up the ranks.
Well, I'll strike first!
Huh?
What's the big idea?
Who the hell are you?
You trying to rob me?
Don't interfere with my shopping.
Excuse me, could I get this?
That'll be 3,000 yen.
That's sorta expensive.
Not bad.
Master...
It bothers you that much...
Wait, it's not like that.
I haven't decided to wear a wig
for the rest of my life or anything.
Doctor Kuseno, it's me, Genos.
There's something I'd like
to discuss immediately.
Master Saitama is in a perilous state.
Those synthetic hair implants
made of reinforced fiber...
You said you could implant them
into living skin, correct?
Yes, that's right.
I believe I'll need them after all.
So black is one of the color options?
If we decide to go forward with the
operation, when will you be available?
The sooner the better?
Next Wednesday? I see.
Yes, I'll be accompanying him.
Understood. Let's go with that day.
Thank you for all of your help.
Master Saitama!
Are you free next Wednesday?
Stop trying to stick reinforced fiber
into my head without my permission.
I'm going to enter a martial
arts tournament wearing this.
As Charanko.
It's today?
Yup. See you later.
I'm gonna go try out this
martial arts thing.